Jhal Hello
Hello Friends I am Deepak Kumar
welcome once again after searching for our channel I hope
you all are well
I hope all the accused are at
home, once again
with a new video I will
tell you which are the companies that we should
buy and that top company we should buy, I
told you in the video that that
company is this company's agent,
in this video I will tell you that we should buy, so
today's topic and if you have
not subscribed to our channel then you guys
need me, so without wasting time let's
start today's video chat that
which are the top companies whose polythene
we should buy and we will also
compare about it, which are the best
companies which we can compare and take home policy
so that these things do not come in our mind that we have to
try this company,
then let's start
[Music]
that the first company whose name I will take for you today is
this company, you
all know Char Help India's
oldest  It is a standalone company. If you
can book this insurance company,
it is India's largest companies. What is
this enrollment called? I will
tell you further. If we talk about this company, then the
company is Apollo Munich, whose name has been
changed. We also know it by the name of Mani,
its name has been changed. You
can book the policy of India's largest company. If we talk about the company, then
this company is Max Bupa. You can subscribe to this channel. The
latest
update in this is Max Bupa. The
boom actors of Max Bupa, which appear in
fact, one percent story, Max has sealed it
through lot. So right now the
sincerity corner on the ribbon of Max
Bupa has become two not for big companies. Let's
talk about which is that big company.
It is Religare Delhi, Delhi, Air India
's largest standalone company.
Because of entry fees, we
can go and book the best health insurance policy. The
fifth company which is a bank company,
during this time the company's name is Manipal Cigna,
which we used to know as Cigna.  It was also known as TTK. It's
basically a South Indian company.
Currently, we know it as Manish Shimla.
From here, we
can also go and buy a policy from Jim Prince.
I've named some of the top companies:
StarHelp, Apollo Munich,
Edifice Health Insurance,
Max Bupa Health Insurance, Religare Health
Insurance, and Manipal Health Insurance, formerly known as Sidha.
These five health
insurance companies are among India's top health
insurance companies, or even
standalone health insurance companies. A
standalone company is a
company that relies solely on a single
product. For example, Religare Health Insurance is the only one. It's
Apollo Health Insurance, and Manipal Health
Insurance is the only one that focuses solely on health insurance.
They don't have any other plans.
Single-channel health insurance is the only company that
grows. We
can buy more policies from this top company. There are also
other Chinese companies from which we can email *
Rubai*.  It is not a stand-alone
company, it is a general insurance
company that insures health benefits and many other
things. In this, we
can open a company in a simple building.
Except for life insurance, the insurance is what
we call a general insurance
company. There are five standalone companies like the
Indian General Insurance Company, from
where we can buy a health insurance policy.
So, the
fastest among these is Bajaj
Allianz General Insurance Company Limited, the largest
general insurance company in the private sector of India, from where
we can buy a health insurance policy.
Their products, which are health
insurance, are also
better than the standalone companies that I have mentioned earlier. If you
take the name of the company from the same competition feature, then there is
ICICI Lombard General
Insurance Company Limited and this is
ICICI group. You can buy ICICI
Lombard, ICICI Prudential
Life Insurance. In such a situation,
we
can buy health insurance company from ICICI Lombard,
which is also available with bank teachers and there is also ICICI Lombard.  I will
take the name of the general insurance company
and it is HDFC Ergo General Insurance
Company Limited. This is also a part of SSC group
which is known as ASI General Insurance
Company Limited. We
can also go here and buy health insurance policies. It is a top end company from
where we can
buy policies of these insurance companies for our
family, for our parents.
We can buy policies from here. So now it is not only
in your mind that I have to compare the
policies of this company with my husband,
that the policies of the company have to be seen only as per the
policies of the other companies. We will talk about this later
and we will come to the features of this company
in the coming video.
I have told about the features of these eight companies.
Apart from this, there is a comparison between the two, which
policy will be based on the difference between the two, we will
also discuss this. So
today our topic was
which are the top health insurance companies,
we can buy the policies from here. So
today we will not miss the video, we will talk to
you once again.  It is requested that if
you people have not yet subscribed to our channel, then
it is again requested to you
that you subscribe to our channel
and share the video and press the bell icon
so that the notification of all the upcoming videos
reaches you first
so that you
can know things about it. So, we will meet you once again
with a new video. In this, we will
discuss the policies of every company
so that you can know what are the inches in which company. Till then, I
seek your permission. Thank you. Thank you
so much.